I want you to say it with me slowly, because maybe today we're ready to admit that if you're a Democrat, you are a colonizer who supports G-side.
That's not a stretch, is it? I don't think so.
And the crazy part is that many of you all will say, well, it's better than being a Republican.
And that's why I can't fucking stand you.
You're all slaves, and you love it.
So you deserve what you get, the erosion of your democracy.
You'll soon be the laughingstock of the world.
That works out for less than 50 cents a month.
It's a damn shame.
That's why the children are occupying space in New York, in Boston, in Washington, in Chicago, in San Francisco, in other cities.
Why? Because they're not looking to you as a source of information for them.
Look how long it took you all to talk about what was going on in New York.
It took you two weeks, because the same people that controlled the banks controlled the media.
You all know it, but you're afraid to say it.